freshershome.com 2012-11-30

# Freshershome.com - Privacy Policy!

## Privacy Policy

Freshershome.com, is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains **private**. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**FreshersHome.com** is/will not be reponsible for the illegal content published by the users, if some user posts any content in the Forum or a job ad with a company name and that is not posted by the real company representative or HR, to remove such content please kindly email to webmaster@freshershome.com, we will remove the content immediatly and take action against the user who posted the content by banning the user id and If possible iP address. We can only do this action if proper information is provided, please rest assured that we are monitoring the posts but we cannot guarantee 100% that the information is validated, hence please be cooperative and send a polite email with right information so that we can initiate the content removal or thread/post removal action.

If you find any Fake or a Copied/Duplicate Content that you think is copied by users and posted here let us know we will make sure that such content is taken off.

**Access**

A Job Seeker is entitled to access to his/her own personal data kept with FreshersHome.com and may edit or amend such personal data at any time. 

Retention of Personal Details Subject to legal requirements, the personal data of the Job Seeker will be retained by FreshersHome.com after deactivation of the Service until the Job Seeker formally requests FreshersHome.com to erase his/her own personal data from FreshersHome.com's database.

The Job Seeker can delete his or her own personal data at any time via the Resume profile section of our website. 

**Information Collection and Use**

_Registration_ \-- A user must register in order to utilize the job search and candidate matching service. During registration, a user is required to provide certain categories of information, such as name, address, college information, e-mail address and password. In addition, a user may choose to provide other categories of information, such as career objectives, prior work history, job related skills and other job search related information. Freshershome.com encourages its users to provide all of these fields of information so that users may maximize the effectiveness of the job search and candidate matching services. 

_Gathering Information to Enhance Service_ \-- In addition to the information that you actively provide to Freshershome.com by methods such as completing the registration form, Freshershome.com collects information about how you interact with our site. Freshershome.com collects passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience at the site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. The types of passive information collected by this site include, without limitation, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go on our site, and how long you stay on any part of our site. Passive information does not identify you to Freshershome.com by name, and Freshershome.com does not link your IP address to your personally identifiable information. 

_Referring a Friend_ \-- You can choose to let a friend know about Freshershome.com through our Refer a Friend program. If you choose to use the Refer a Friend program, we will ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address and Freshershome.com will send your friend an e-mail inviting him or her to visit Freshershome.com to learn more about our services. Freshershome.com does not store your friend's contact information. 

_Optional Information_ \-- At various other points during your visit to Freshershome.com, you may be asked to provide information about yourself. For example, you may indicate that you wish to participate in a partner company sponsored contest. At this point your information would become the property of both Freshershome.com and the partner co-sponsoring the contest. In instances such as this, Freshershome.com is not responsible for the information that the partner company receives. Participation in surveys or contests or the use of other services that require the input of additional information is completely voluntary on your part, and you have the choice about whether to disclose the information necessary to use these features of our site. 

**Use of Information**

The information that you supply to Freshershome.com enables us to provide job search and candidate matching services, to the Employers, Recruiters, and consultants. In addition, Freshershome.com uses your information in order to customize our site to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our site. Along with this we gather other important information and keep the data to outself to Improve our quality of service, Advertisements, site layout design and other structural materials. 

_Online Application for a Job_ \-- When applying for a job on Freshershome.com, you respond directly to the employer and this is considered confidential information. Under NO circumstances does Freshershome.com publicize your confidential response to any particular company. It is totally upto you to allow employers to view your personal information [ **Blocked Fields** ] 

_Contacting by E-Mail / News letter Service_ \-- Freshershome.com may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding updates at the Freshershome.com site. The frequency of these messages will vary depending upon your profile. In addition, we may send you free informational newsletters or notices relating to topics that may be of special interest to you, including job opportunities and job advice. Finally, if you specifically provide Freshershome.com with permission at the time of registration, you may also receive commercial e-mails. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to opt-out of receiving many of the newsletters and/or commercial e-mails whenever Freshershome.com sends such messages. However certain communications from Freshershome.com such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Weekly Newsletter are considered part of Freshershome.com membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. E-mail messages from third parties are not governed by the opt-out provisions of this Privacy Policy, but all such third parties are strongly encouraged to include opt-out procedures in their messages to you. 

**Transfer of Data**

Freshershome.com does not **rent, sell, or share personal information** about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted Employers, Who inturn use this information for setting up interviews, walk-ins, off campus drives, No Personal Information is shared unless you allow them to view the currently blocked items. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * You can edit your Freshershome.com Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 
  * New categories of communication may be added to the Subscriptions page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

**Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. 
  * Your Freshershome.com account Information is password-protected.

**We At FreshersHome.com,** we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit FreshersHome.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FreshersHome.com Website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to FreshersHome.com users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on FreshersHome.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Bangalore real estate ads to someone in Bangalore, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Other Provisions**

 _Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy_ \-- Your use of this site [FreshersHome.com] indicates an acceptance of the terms of the **Privacy Policy**. Freshershome.com reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

**Contacting the FreshersHome.com**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our site, please [Contact Us](http://www.freshershome.com/jobs/contact-us.php "Contact us").
